txtnation.com 2006-02-09

# txtNation :: Creating Mobile Interaction between Businesses and Consumers | Mobile Solutions

**  
Privacy Policy**

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for txtNation. If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should contact:

**Email:** [privacy@txtnation.com](mailto:privacy@txtnation.com)

**1\. Interpretation**  
In these Conditions:

**Users**

| 

means the users of txtNation services. The end-user and the partner.  
  
---|---  
  
TOP

**2\. Information collection and Usage**  
txtNation collects information from our users at several different points on our website and in our services as described below. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. txtNation has the right to store data that may comes from an information provider.

TOP

**3\. Registration**  
All required information is used to provide users with services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide location information (such as home and work addresses), but encouraged so we can provide a more personalised experience on our site and services.

TOP

**4\. Cookies**  
**4.1** A cookie is a small file that your web browser places on your computer's hard drive to store information. Our site uses cookies to provide visitors with a personalised experience. We use two types of cookies on our site. The first kind ensures that once our users log on to the site and service, they don't have to log in a second time while navigating the site. These cookies are deleted from your hard disk at the end of each session. The second kind of cookie is set only at a user's request, and used to save the email and password one uses to log on to the site and service. It remains on your hard drive once you have closed your browser. Once the cookie is in place, we can log you on automatically by accessing this piece of information. Session-based cookies must be turned on in your browser settings to use the site and service. To save your email and password, all cookies must be turned on.

**4.2** Some of our business partners may use cookies on our website (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

TOP

**5\. Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track users movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

TOP

**6\. Sharing Data**  
**6.1** We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. Aggregated demographic information is not linked to any information that can identify any individual person.

**6.2** We partner with various third parties to provide specific services. When users use these services through txtNation, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for these third parties to provide these services. These parties may not use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

**6.3** We may use your information and activities within the site to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce the txtNation Terms of Use. When compelled by law, txtNation cooperates with all law enforcement inquiries and with third parties reasonably seeking to enforce their intellectual property or other legal rights. Moreover, txtNation may (and by using the service you authorize txtNation to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials, as txtNation, in its sole discretion, believes necessary or appropriate to comply with the law.

TOP

**7\. Selling Data**  
We reserve the right to sell aggregated demographic data or stored data to third parties. Aggregated demographic information is not linked to any information that can identify any individual person.

TOP

**8\. Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that txtNation is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site and service.

TOP

**9\. Newsletter and Partner Mailings**  
We offer users the options of subscribing to our newsletter and receiving partner mailings.

TOP

**10\. Security**  
**10.1** txtNation takes every precaution to protect our users' information. However, we cannot guarantee this and you should not expect, that personally identifiable information or private communications will remain private under all circumstances. For example, third parties ("hackers") may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or stored information. We do not assume any responsibility or liability for any information you submit to or receive from txtNation. We also do not assume any responsibility or liability for your own or a third party's use or misuse of information transmitted or received during use of the site or service.

**10.2** At present, we do not collect sensitive information such as credit card numbers. At the point in the future that we do so, we will encrypt that information, and protect it with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'.

**10.3** We also use commercially reasonable efforts to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they must do to ensure our customers' information is protected.

TOP

**11\. Special Offers**  
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt out section below.

TOP

**12\. Choice / Opt Out**  
**12.1** Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt out of receiving these communications by emailing Technical Support at [support@txtnation.com](mailto:support@txtnation.com).

**12.2** Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party.

TOP

**13\. Availability**  
The txtNation services are not available to children under the age of 16. If txtNation becomes aware that a user under the age of 16 has used or is attempting to use the service, we will notify the user that he is not eligible to use the service. 

TOP

**14\. Notification of Changes**  
**14.1** If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

**14.2** It is our policy to comply with all applicable laws and regulations, as they may be modified from time to time. If any portion of this privacy statement conflicts with any applicable law or regulation, the applicable law or regulation will supersede the conflicting part of this privacy statement. 

TOP

**15\. Information that you provide to us  
****15.1** iBill receives and stores all information that you enter on our website and our billing pages. This includes; a) credit card sign-up page: the url you are purchasing goods or services from, your e-mail address, your language preference, your credit card number, your expiration date, your first name, your last name, your address, your city, your state, your zip, your country, and your agreement to be bound by iBill's terms and conditions; b) check sign-up page: the url you are purchasing goods or services from, your bank's aba routing number, your checking account number, your check number, your e-mail address, your first name, your last name, your date of birth, your phone number, your street address, your city, your state, your zip code, the name of the person on the account, your agreement to be bound by iBill's terms and conditions; and c) telephone invoice billing: your telephone number. You are obligated to provide iBill with accurate and up-to-date information, and failure to provide iBill with such information could void any Agreement between you and iBill. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as processing your purchase request, responding to customer service inquiries, loss prevention, improving our service, communicating with you, and allowing our clients to provide customer service and fulfill their obligations to you. 

TOP
